e-ir.info 2007-11-28

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how e-IR uses and protects any information that you give e-IR when you use this website.

e-IR is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

e-IR may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 11th November 2007.

We may collect the following information:

  * Name.
  * Contact information including email address.
  * Past or currently affiliated academic institution.

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better resource, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our resources.
  * We may periodically send informational emails about new website content, functions or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable electronic procedures available within our content management system to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to user needs.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please [email e-IR](mailto:info@e-ir.info).

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please [email us](mailto:info@e-ir.info) as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
